<?xml version="1.0" standalone="yes"?>
<rss xmlns:sparkle="http://www.andymatuschak.org/xml-namespaces/sparkle" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>RepoBar</title>
        <item>
            <title>0.1.2</title>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 22:40:17 +0100</pubDate>
            <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/steipete/RepoBar/main/appcast.xml</link>
            <sparkle:version>3</sparkle:version>
            <sparkle:shortVersionString>0.1.2</sparkle:shortVersionString>
            <sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>10.13</sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>
            <description><![CDATA[<ul><li>iOS app preview (not finished, not in the App Store yet): repo list/cards, activity feed, detail drill‑downs, login/settings, icons/branding, and continued auth/UI polish.</li><li>CLI parity expansion: new repo list subcommands (releases, CI runs, discussions, tags, branches, contributors, commits, activity) plus `--owner/--mine` filters.</li><li>CLI local actions + settings: sync/rebase/reset/checkout, branch/worktree listings, Finder/Terminal open; pin/hide and settings show/set; installer for `repobar`.</li><li>Changelog UX: submenu preview improvements plus Markdown rendering upgrades (block layout, scrollable preview, header alignment).</li><li>Changelog UX: show the first released section headline in the submenu badge (skips Unreleased).</li><li>Changelog UX: prefetch on repo submenu open and refresh the badge after load.</li><li>Changelog UX: switch to Swift Markdown AST parsing for cross-platform block rendering.</li><li>Releases submenu: show latest release name next to the count badge.</li><li>Menu customization: Display settings to reorder/hide main menu and repo submenu items (reset to defaults), with spacing tweaks.</li><li>Logging/diagnostics: swift-log integration with OSLog + optional file logging; debug logging settings for macOS/iOS.</li><li>Reliability: menu rehydrate on attach, invalidate empty menu cache, stabilize contribution header heatmap size, limit “More” submenus to 20 entries.</li><li>Repo access + errors: include org/collaborator repos, improve repo detail error messaging, cache discussions capability and hide disabled entries.</li></ul>
]]></description>
            <enclosure url="https://github.com/steipete/RepoBar/releases/download/v0.1.2/RepoBar-0.1.2.zip" length="14747306" type="application/octet-stream" sparkle:edSignature="87cgD/YmHR1SMRuzXlly+SSPzGaaYUHWH4L9Wqxp0liM3p46/4c34Cn4AckMB2odMvJ9gSZDXcIt3qigZ8KnCA=="/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>0.1.1</title>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 03:08:30 +0100</pubDate>
            <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/steipete/RepoBar/main/appcast.xml</link>
            <sparkle:version>2</sparkle:version>
            <sparkle:shortVersionString>0.1.1</sparkle:shortVersionString>
            <sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>10.13</sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>
            <description><![CDATA[<ul><li>Fix CLI: allow invoking bundled `repobarcli` directly (argv0 normalization).</li></ul>
]]></description>
            <enclosure url="https://github.com/steipete/RepoBar/releases/download/v0.1.1/RepoBar-0.1.1.zip" length="11338886" type="application/octet-stream" sparkle:edSignature="nJ4XzYOz3dPYXdEXPJUnYCNJjdnR/j9l7yy5lgT7vxvr8yhe3e39B9Gh4Maf+Nqg5pNsL3xVPcCgbAraiXj9Ag=="/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>0.1.0</title>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 02:17:28 +0100</pubDate>
            <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/steipete/RepoBar/main/appcast.xml</link>
            <sparkle:version>1</sparkle:version>
            <sparkle:shortVersionString>0.1.0</sparkle:shortVersionString>
            <sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>10.13</sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>First public release of RepoBar — a macOS menubar dashboard for GitHub repo health, activity, and local project state.</p><h3>Highlights</h3><ul><li>Live repository cards with CI status, activity, releases, and rate‑limit awareness.</li><li>Rich submenus for recent pull requests, issues, releases, workflow runs, discussions, tags, branches, and commits.</li><li>Local Git state surfaced directly in the menu (branch, upstream/ahead/behind, dirty files, worktrees) with safe actions.</li><li>Contribution heatmap header and global activity feed.</li><li>Fast, native menu UI with adaptive layout and caching for performance.</li></ul><h3>Feature overview</h3><ul><li>**Menubar experience**</li></ul><p>- Repository cards with stats (stars, forks, issues, last push), CI badge, activity preview, and optional heatmaps. - Pinned/hidden repos, menu filters, and configurable sorting. - Empty/logged‑out states that explain what to do next.</p><ul><li>**Recent activity &amp; insights**</li></ul><p>- Pull requests, issues, releases, workflow runs, discussions, tags, branches, and commit lists per repo. - Global activity menu with recent events and commits. - Activity links deep‑link to the most relevant GitHub pages.</p><ul><li>**Local projects &amp; Git actions**</li></ul><p>- Local repo status: current branch, upstream sync, dirty counts, and file lists. - Worktree and branch menus with metadata and quick actions. - Open in Finder/Terminal, checkout, create branch/worktree, sync/rebase/reset.</p><ul><li>**Auth &amp; API**</li></ul><p>- OAuth login, secure token refresh, and shared core used by the CLI. - Rate‑limit awareness and caching to minimize GitHub API usage.</p><ul><li>**Contribution heatmap**</li></ul><p>- Header heatmap (cached) with the ability to refresh and clear cache. - Optional menu heatmaps aligned to a week‑based date range.</p><ul><li>**Performance &amp; reliability**</li></ul><p>- Cached repo details, activity, and heatmaps for a snappy menu. - Menu layout caching, reuse of menu items, and debounced refresh. - Timeouts and graceful fallback for slow network requests.</p><ul><li>**CLI** (`repobar`)</li></ul><p>- Status and repo listings with filters, JSON/plain output, and release info. - Commands for issues/pulls lists, pinned/hidden scopes, and activity age filtering.</p><ul><li>**Updates**</li></ul><p>- Sparkle updater for signed builds with update‑ready menu entry and full dialog flow.</p><ul><li>**Developer tooling**</li></ul><p>- SwiftPM + pnpm scripts, lint/format, Apollo GraphQL codegen. - Release pipeline with signing, notarization, and Sparkle appcast generation.</p>
]]></description>
            <enclosure url="https://github.com/steipete/RepoBar/releases/download/v0.1.0/RepoBar-0.1.0.zip" length="10884750" type="application/octet-stream" sparkle:edSignature="3pNVtUb67wcMhK6TqaToyQsAkeeAFeMEmDXPSLo8bsZI1pLFPENkURYGg3J3iBvO7Sn5w5UPyJQ6HsMaFT6OBg=="/>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>